So hot!
Cute.
They're all coming in...
Mommy.
I'm looking at the camera.
How's it going?
Pokey.
Pokey!
It's Yuzumi!
Yuzumi.
Yuzumi!
Hello. - Hello.
Hello.
I'm Minami Koike of Kurasaka 46.
And, ta-da!
I'm Ou.
Long time no see.
It's been about a year.
I'm doing a project for Ban-chan.
I know this might be a bit of a surprise to you guys, but...
I'm sorry, Pomik.
Hey!
Please take a moment to calm down.
We've added two new members to our family!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Two more dogs!
I have a family
So now I have a child
I have 3 kids.
I'm a mother
This one...
Oh, she's gone.
I just saw him...
I just saw this little guy coming at me face to face.
His name is Potato in hiragana.
And this Pomeranian...
This little guy...
He's so fluffy.
Please don't fight.
She was so fluffy, she looked like a spider.
So we named him "Prum" in French.
They're all in the "puppy-poo-poo" line!
I'm looking forward to working with you!
Today I was a little nervous about seeing all three of them together by myself.
I felt a little uneasy.
So I asked two members who are very, very close
So I've asked two members who are very, very close to each other to come.
Please come.
Ta-da!
The Endo sisters are here.
Here they are!
Riko and Hikari are here.
We've already had a good time with them.
The kids are especially attached to them.
All of them.
Riko and Hikari.
We're all here today.
Here we are!
I hope we can go to a dock run or a cafe or something.
It's so hot today
It's so hot!
We haven't walked outside yet.
I'd like to go for a walk.
They don't fight?
They're fighting.
No, they're not.
They don't fight?
Potato is pudding.
Prue's gonna get mad because he's gonna find her on top of Prue.
Can we go in?
Are you okay?
I'll give you a lift.
This is Pom.
It's hard.
Thank you. Thank you.
Ouch.
Okay, we're at the dock run.
Oh, my God.
Are you okay?
I just need a minute.
No way. Potatoes...
No way.
Potatoes.
Oh, no.
It's finally time!
Height, right?
Pouliot.
It's our first time here, so we're all a little nervous.
Pote is here.
Pote is here!
Pote and Riko are totally in love with each other.
Hikaru seems to be in love with her, too.
I knew it! Mi-chan dumped me!
Pom...
Pom is the type that doesn't run at the dock run.
He's so friendly. He's so friendly.
He's good at getting people to like him.
Pom is still on my skirt.
All three of them are white. How can I get a good picture of them?
Pom Pom, where are you going?
There's a toy.
So cute!
I wonder if I can throw it.
Pokey Pokey.
Everyone's free.
Prue is tall.
Prue doesn't move much.
Puteh!
He's sniffing and sniffing.
I don't know what to do.
No, no, no, no, no...
Puteh!
He's so cute.
Cute.
All white. Everyone.
They all happen to be pure white, don't they?
Miisan is pure white, too.
Hey!
Everyone's all around you, Miichan.
They're all around you!
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
She's far away!
So cute!
I want to show you.
Oh, my...
I'll be in the shadow.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's hot in the shade, isn't it?
It's hot today, isn't it?
It's hot, isn't it?
You're all in the shade, smart kids.
Oh, he's gone.
Mom, he's gone.
Come here. Come here.
Come on.
It's hot.
They're not fair.
That's hot.
You can go there, but I'm gonna take it down.
Winter.
Potato, potato, potato.
Are you okay?
You're with my mother.
I'm fine with my mom.
Oh, my God.
He's so cute.
Potato.
They're all cute, the people ones.
I jumped on it.
So cute.
They all came in.
Hikari, the popular girl
So cute!
They're fighting over her.
Really? So cute!
They're fighting over Hikari.
I'm so happy.
She's so popular.
Would you guys like some water?
I'll leave it here.
I'll have some water.
Have a glass of water, Puri.
Have a drink, Puri.
I'll have some too.
On my feet.
It's a hot time of year for all of us.
They're all sweating their skin off.
That's hot.
You're drinking water.
You're hot.
So hot.
Oh, my God, they're sweating so much.
It's hot, isn't it?
Let's go to the water place.
Let's go to the water.
Hey, let's go to the pool first.
It's your first time, actually.
Actually, it's my first time in a pool.
What are you gonna do?
Dad, can we go?
You want to go?
Yo.
Oh, wow.
It's cool.
Isn't it cool?
Wait, are you sitting down too low?
Are you okay?
Drink some water.
Here, drink this water.
Sit down, potato.
Oh, I'm soaking wet.
I'm soaking wet, too.
Let's get better.
We're soaking wet.
It's like summer.
It feels good, doesn't it?
He's so cute.
It's so cute.
Pool.
They're all strong.
I'm soaking wet.
Oh,
Ah,
They're all gone.
Oh, my God.
It feels nice and cool.
You're squinting.
He's so cute.
You're so cute.
Look at me for the camera.
How's that?
Squint like this.
Oh, they're both lying down.
I'm soaking wet.
How are you guys going to get home?
What are we going to do?
Oh,
Oh, God.
Just put your feet up in the bathtub.
You're both soaking wet.
You guys are so cute
Pom, pom, pom
That's my eldest son
Pom pom
Pom Pom.
Come here.
That felt good.
Hey, don't do that.
Come here, Pom Pom. Come here.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
That felt good.
There's a photo booth right here, so let's all go to the diagasa and take a picture.
Let's take a picture.
I don't know where we're supposed to go in here.
Where do you think? Here?
Can we put it in the middle? Here.
Hom, take a hint.
Dong!
They all look like people.
They're so cute.
I think there's some kind of indoor
I think there's an indoor dock run.
Let's go to the indoor dock run.
Let's go!
Let's go, Pom!
I'm going in.
Oh, my God.
That's great. - That's great.
That's Laure's pool.
You wanna go?
You're going?
You're going, huh?
Pom, I'm going.
I'm going.
Let's go.
Pouliot is coming too.
Kohté, you coming?
Coté.
DAVE.
What do you think? Strange?
What the hell is this?
It's strange, isn't it?
What about you, Pom?
What's Pom? You're a questioner.
You're a quiet boy, aren't you?
Pomu, you're a big boy.
So cute!
POTEE, you're so full of energy.
Ooh!
Don't break it.
POTEE-chan, POTEE-chan, POTEE-chan, POTEE-chan, let's go, POTEE-chan.
Oh, I think it's this way.
I don't see any wind.
Chitty-chitty, chitty-chitty, chitty-chitty, chitty-chitty, chitty-chitty, chitty-chitty.
By bugs.
By insects
Bugs
Distance this way
This way
If you're so inclined, there seems to be a café.
Let's go together.
Let's go.
Let's eat.
We're gonna eat.
So cute
My dear junior
Don't worry.
I'll have to change my last name to Endo too.
Oh, old dragon perm
Mom, Ode-chan's here.
Where's Mom?
Where's Mommy?
Pom is downstairs.
She's under the desk.
He's so cute.
Polly, you're soaking wet.
All the way down.
Full of energy.
Cute.
Thank you.
The dog that eats it is behind me. He said, "Mine?
"Mine? And he says, "Mine?
I love it when you eat fries.
Thank you very much.
He's so cute.
So cute.
I wish Pom could eat this.
Cute serving.
Oh, Pom is peeking now.
Pom is peeking.
I'm sorry. Thank you.
Come here, Pom.
I don't want to hold it.
Yo.
Oh!
Potato paints himself.
Potato first.
This is for you, Mr. Pob.
Potato genre.
We're going to do this together, and then we're going to do this together, and then we're going to do this together, and then we're going to do this together, and then we're going to do this together with Muscle. I haven't seen any.
Tom, you want some? Want some?
Want some?
Eat slowly, slowly, slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly.
Watch me eat.
That's what I said in one bite.
Are you tasting it?
I tasted it.
I'm so melodramatic, aren't I?
And now that my favorite broccoli is in front of me...
Oh, I'm drooling.
Ahhh...
You're drooling.
Drool, drool, drool, drool.
Want some? We'll have some too.
Hey, you want some?
You want some?
Oh, you two.
They're fighting.
Bon appétit.
Ah!
That was fast.
She eats slowly.
That's unusual.
I'll have some of that.
Give me some of that.
Oh, my God.
I'm falling, I'm falling.
That was fast.
How'd it taste? Was it good?
It all went so fast.
Here comes the face.
Let's go, turtle!
And the broccoli.
Eat slowly, eat slowly.
Slowly, slowly, slowly, slowly...
Oh, he's so cute.
I didn't say yes, but now...
You don't eat tomatoes with this gesture?
I've never eaten a tomato.
Tomatoes are not for everyone.
Which one?
I don't know if I can do it.
I don't like it.
But...
Let's eat rice.
I ate.
Did you eat?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh! The head of time and the kame place of time
I'm in the head of the time and the eyes of Ahmed Ou
I said, "I'm in the eye of the ISA câmb madam!
Everyone can eat tomatoes!
I'm in trouble.
I saw this on the Sakurazaka channel once.
I was talking about how the book looks like Yui Takemoto if she were a member
I wanted to guess which one of the members the two of them look like.
If it were a face, who would it be?
Looks like Nade-chan.
I might know.
She's a princess with only boys.
What do you think of Tsurihu's personality?
Mature.
She's like an adult.
When we went out...
He's always sulking.
Karin?
You're right, they do look alike.
Yeah.
Like Karin? Her personality...
Like you don't have it.
Like, "I'll be fine anywhere.
I see.
When we were in the ball pool...
Yeah.
He was so calm.
That was amazing.
You're so confident everywhere.
I'll be watching.
My word.
What about me? What's my word?
What about me? I'm?
What about me? I'm...
2! Wow, that's a tough one.
If it's a personality, who is it? Is he cheerful? I'm like, "How are you? She's energetic. She's energetic. Everyone's energetic.
She's shy. But she's like a cousin.
If it's a personality, it might be Itoha.
Do any of the members have a dog? There are a lot of them.
We were talking about how we'd like to get together with other Sakurazaka members who have dogs.
We wanted to have an athletic meet with the members' dogs.
We'd like to shorten the 50-meter run to a 10-meter run, and measure the time of each dog.
Potatoes are too fast!
Absolutely not.
That's true.
Let's get all the members' dogs together.
Doggy Tomo!
I hope everyone can make friends amongst their poochies.
Today is really the day that this my
I'm sure it's great.
three dogs together for the project.
Thank you so much for coming.
I really appreciate it.
I think it was a lot of fun.
So...
Thank you.
You're so cute.
She's cute.
I posed like this.
Oh!
I'm gonna have to pose like this.
Let me see your face.
I'm the last one who idolizes you.
I'm thinking of having a field day next time.
I want to go play.
So...
I want to.
I want you to come as a cheering group for Koi Keke.
It was fun, wasn't it?
Good for you... for once.
They're so cute... all the dogs.
I liked the Endo sisters and their dog, Koi Keke.
If you enjoyed the show, please click the "Good" button and subscribe to our channel!
Thank you very much!